<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<knimeNode icon="./bert_predictor.png" type="Predictor" xmlns="http://knime.org/node/v2.10" xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:schemaLocation="http://knime.org/node/v2.10 http://knime.org/node/v2.10.xsd">
    <name>BERT Predictor</name>
    
    <shortDescription>
        Applies a BERT Classification model to the input table.
    </shortDescription>
    
    <fullDescription>
        <intro>
        	Applies a BERT Classification model to the input table.
        </intro>
        <tab name="Settings">
        	<option name="Sentence column">
        		A column with a plain text (String) or Documents, that contains text to be classified.
        		No special pre-processing is needed.
        	</option>
        	<option name="Batch size">The number of rows to feed to the model simultaniously.
        	During prediction it is typically possible to use a larger batch size than during model training.</option>
        	<option name="Change prediction column name">
        		If active a column with provided name will be created in the output table.
        		Otherwise the default name will be used for the column with predictions.
        	</option>
        	<option name="Append individual class probabilities">
        		If active the columns with class probabilities will be created in the output table.
        	</option>
        	<option name="Suffix for probability columns">
        		If not empty the suffix will be added to every column name for class probabilities columns.
        	</option>
        </tab>
        <tab name="Multi-label">
        	<option name="Use custom threshold for assigning the classes">
        		If active it is possible to change the probability threshold for assigning the class. By default class is assigned by the biggest probability value.
        	</option>
        	<option name="Probability threshold">
        		The class is assigned if the class probability is equal or higher then the value. Several classes might be assigned.
        	</option>
        	<option name="Fixed number of classes per prediction">
        		If active it is possible to set up the desired number of classes for a prediction.
        	</option>
        	<option name="Number of classes per prediction">
        		The fixed number of classes that will be assigned to the prediction.
        	</option>
        	<option name="Use custom class separator">
        		If active it is possible to enter the separation character for the prediction. Prediction is represented as a string with separated values.
        	</option>
        	<option name="Class separator">
        		A character that separates multiple labels for prediction.
        	</option>
        </tab>
        <tab name="Python">
    		<option name="Python">
    			Select one of the Python execution environment options:
    			<ul>
        			<li>use default Python environment for the Redfield BERT Nodes (can be configured on the preference page)</li>
        			<li>use Conda environment from a Conda flow variable (only selectable if such a flow variable is available)</li>
        		</ul>
    		</option>
        </tab>
    </fullDescription>
    
    <ports>
		<inPort name="BERT Classifier" index="0">BERT Classifier</inPort>
		<inPort name="Data Table" index="1">Data Table</inPort>
		<outPort name="Output Table" index="0">Output table</outPort>
    </ports>    
</knimeNode>
